OKAY...
( gasping )
NOW, LISTEN, I'M GOING
TO BE MOVING OUT
SO YOU ARE GOING TO BE
IN CHARGE OF PAYING THE RENT.
RIGHT.
AND WHEN IS THAT DUE?
FIRST OF THE MONTH.
AND THAT'S EVERY MONTH?
NO, JUST THE MONTHS YOU ACTUALLY
WANT TO LIVE HERE.
AH...
OKAY, HERE'S THE PHONE BILL.
OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S OUR PHONE NUMBER.
NOW, LOOK, I KNOW
I KIND OF SPRUNG THIS WHOLE
"ME MOVING OUT ON YOU" THING,
SO WHY DON'T I JUST...
WHY DON'T I JUST COVER
YOU FOR A WHILE?
NO, NO, NO WAY.
JOEY TRIBBIANI DOES
NOT TAKE CHARITY...
ANYMORE.
IT'S NOT CHARITY, JOE.
NO. FORGET IT, OKAY?
I MEAN, THANKS, BUT I'M DONE
TAKING MONEY FROM
YOU, ALL RIGHT?
I CAN TAKE CARE
OF MYSELF.
NOW, WHAT'S
NEXT? COME ON.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT,
HERE'S THE ELECTRIC BILL.
THIS IS HOW MUCH WE
PAY FOR ELECTRIC?!
WELL, YEAH.
( muttering )
SO WE'LL DO THE REST OF
THE BILLS LATER, THEN?
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
IS JOEY GOING TO HAVE
TO GIVE UP THE APARTMENT?
WELL, I HOPE NOT.
I TRIED TO OFFER HIM
SOME MONEY, BUT HE
WOULDN'T TAKE IT.
WELL, HOW MUCH
DO YOU THINK HE NEEDS?
I FIGURED $1,500
WOULD COVER HIM
FOR A FEW
MONTHS, YOU KNOW?
BUT I HAVE TO TRICK
HIM INTO TAKING IT
SO I DON'T HURT
HIS PRIDE.
YEAH, WELL, WHY DON'T YOU
HIRE HIM AS AN ACTOR?
YOU COULD HAVE HIM DRESS UP
AND PUT ON LITTLE SKITS--
JUST WHATEVER YOU WANT.
WELL, THAT WOULD HELP
THE PRIDE THING.
HEY.
HEY, WOW,
YOU LOOK GREAT.
DO YOU WANT TO MOVE IN
WITH ME TOMORROW?
OKAY.
OKAY. SO, WHAT DO YOU GIRLS
HAVE PLANNED FOR TONIGHT?
WELL, INSTEAD
OF BEING SAD
THAT TONIGHT'S MY LAST
THAT NIGHT WITH RACHEL
WE THOUGHT WE'D
GO OUT TO DINNER
AND CELEBRATE THE FACT
THAT RACHEL'S MOVING
IN WITH PHOEBE.
AND ALSO, MY BIRTHDAY.
IT'S NOT YOUR BIRTHDAY.
WHAT A MEAN THING TO SAY.
I WOULD NEVER TELL YOU
IT WAS NOT YOUR BIRTHDAY.
HEY.
Phoebe:
SO, YOU GUYS HAVE
ANYTHING PLANNED
FOR THE BIG LAST NIGHT?
WELL, INSTEAD
OF JUST HANGING OUT
WE FIGURED WE'D DO NOTHING.
WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA--
KNICKS SEASON OPENER TONIGHT.
I THOUGHT MAYBE YOU GUYS
WOULD COME OVER AND WATCH IT.
I DON'T KNOW, ROSS.
NOT IF YOU'RE
GOING TO TALK ABOUT
HOW YOU GAVE UP
A CAREER IN BASKETBALL
TO BECOME A PALEONTOLOGIST.
I DID GIVE UP
A CAREER IN BASKETBALL
TO BECOME A PALEONTOLOGIST.
( groaning )
PHEEBS, I WAS WONDERING...
YOU'RE NOT DRESSED YET?
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO START
HAVING FUN IN 15 MINUTES.
WELL, AND CLEARLY,
NOT A MINUTE SOONER.
RACHEL, YOU ARE PACKED,
THOUGH, RIGHT?
I MEAN, PLEASE TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE PACKED.
OF COURSE I'M PACKED.
MONICA, RELAX.
I JUST WANTED TO ASK
PHOEBE HER OPINION
ON WHAT I SHOULD WEAR TONIGHT.
MY GOD, I CANNOT GET
A MINUTE OF PEACE AROUND HERE.
OH, MY GOD!
YOU'RE NOT PACKED YET.
MONICA'S JUST GOING
TO KILL YOU.
YEAH, I-I KNOW.
WELL, WHAT YOU'RE WEARING
IS FINE FOR THAT.
RACHEL, I NEED TO TALK...
YOU'RE NOT PACKED!
YOU'RE NOT PACKED
EVEN A LITTLE BIT.
SURPRISE!
WHAT?
DON'T GET MAD, 'CAUSE, LOOK
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED--
SO I-I STARTED PACKING
AND THEN I REALIZED,
"WHAT AM I DOING?
I AM LOUSY AT
PACKING," RIGHT?
BUT YOU LOVE PACKING
SO AS A GIFT TO YOU
ON OUR LAST NIGHT...
TA-DA.
RIGHT. I'LL BE COORDINATOR.
OH, MY GOD, I'M SO SORRY--
I DIDN'T GET YOU ANYTHING.
OKAY, LOOK, EVERYBODY
HAS TO HELP, OKAY?
PHOEBE, YOU CAN HELP,
CAN'T YOU?
I HAVE PLANS.
YOU HAVE PLANS WITH US.
THAT'S... RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT,
CHANDLER CAN MAKE BOXES
ROSS CAN WRAP
AND JOEY CAN LIFT THINGS.
NOW, PHOEBE, GO TELL THE GUYS
THEY HAVE TO HELP OUT.
OKAY.
MY GOD, THANK YOU!
HURRY. MONICA'S GOING
TO MAKE YOU PACK--
SHE'S GOT JOBS
FOR EVERYONE.
NOW, IT'S TOO LATE FOR ME,
BUT SAVE YOURSELVES.
Monica:
OKAY, THE MOVERS
WILL BE HERE
IN 11 HOURS.
RACHEL HAS NOT PACKED.
NOW, EVERYBODY HAS TO HELP.
CHANDLER, WE'RE GOING
TO START...
NO, I-I-I HAVE PLANS
WITH JOEY.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WERE GOING TO DO NOTHING.
YES, BUT FOR THE LAST TIME.
( sniffling )
OKAY, FINE.
NOW, ROSS...
OH, BUT I-I CAN'T DO IT.
WHY NOT?
DON'T YOU HAVE BEN?
BECAUSE...
I HAVE BEN.
IT'S ALMOST 8:00.
IT'S ALMOST PAST HIS BEDTIME.
WHERE IS HE?
HE'S AT A DINNER PARTY.
IS HE REALLY COMING? BECAUSE
I CAN SEE INTO YOUR APARTMENT.
OF COURSE HE IS.
UH, WHAT, YOU THINK I'D JUST USE
MY SON AS-AS AN EXCUSE?
WHAT KIND OF FATHER
DO YOU THINK I AM?
ALL RIGHT, SORRY.
I GOT TO GO MAKE
A FAKE BEN.
HERE IT IS--
OUR LAST PIZZAS TOGETHER
AS ROOMMATES.
I WISH I'D KNOWN YOU
WERE GOING TO DO THAT.
I ORDERED CHINESE.
OH, WELL, THAT'S OKAY.
HEY, ACTUALLY, IN A WAY,
IT'S KIND OF NICE.
YOU KNOW, OUR LAST
DINNER TOGETHER--
ME, BRINGING THE FOOD
OF MY ANCESTORS
YOU, THE FOOD OF YOURS.
HUH?
( chuckling )
SAY, JOE, I HAD A STRANGE IDEA
FOR WHAT WE COULD DO
FOR OUR LAST NIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE PLAY
A LITTLE FOOSBALL FOR MONEY?
ARE YOU CRAZY?
YOU HAVEN'T BEATEN ME ONCE SINCE
MY INJURY-PLAGUED '97 SEASON.
IT'D BE EASIER
IF YOU JUST GIVE ME YOUR MONEY.
YES, IT WOULD.
( clears throat )
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO $50?
OKAY, YOU'RE ON.
OKAY, LET'S PLAY.
THE BIG GAME--
ITALY VERSUS...
CHINA, APPARENTLY.
OH, LOOK...
IT'S THE ROLLERBLADES.
OH, GOD...
DO YOU REMEMBER
WHEN WE GOT THESE?
NO.
AW, I GUESS YOU WEREN'T THERE.
YOU GUYS, WE SAID WE WERE
GOING TO HAVE FUN.
COME ON, HEY.
REMEMBER THE TIME...?
( laughing )
YOU DON'T REMEMBER?
I'M SORRY, PHEEBS.
I GUESS I'M JUST REALLY SAD
THAT I'M LEAVING.
I'M GOING TO MISS
YOU SO MUCH.
WELL, THIS DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
SO SAD, THOUGH, YOU KNOW?
MAYBE INSTEAD
OF JUST THINKING ABOUT
HOW MUCH YOU'RE GOING
TO MISS EACH OTHER
YOU SHOULD, LIKE,
THINK ABOUT SOME OF THE THINGS
THAT YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MISS.
I DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANYTHING.
COME ON, THERE'S GOT
TO BE SOMETHING.
NOPE.
SHE'S PERFECT.
HMM.
I HAVE ONE.
GREAT. OKAY, YOU CAN GO FIRST.
UH, WELL, I GUESS I'M NOT
GOING TO MISS THE FACT...
THAT YOU'RE NEVER ALLOWED
TO MOVE THE PHONE PEN.
GOOD. THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
OKAY, MONICA, ANYTHING?
YOU KNOW, DOES RACHEL MOVE
THE PHONE PEN?
AW, SOMETIMES...
ALWAYS, ACTUALLY.
OKAY, GOOD. THERE YOU GO.
DOESN'T EVERYONE FEEL BETTER?
IT'S NOT JUST
THE PHONE PEN.
I NEVER GET MY MESSAGES.
YOU GET YOUR MESSAGES.
YEAH, WELL, I DON'T THINK
IT REALLY COUNTS
IF YOU HAVE TO READ THEM
OFF THE BACK OF YOUR HAND
AFTER YOU'VE FALLEN ASLEEP
ON THE COUCH.
SO-SO, YOU MISSED
A MESSAGE FROM WHO?
CHANDLER OR YOUR MOM?
OR CHANDLER?
OR YOUR MOM?
GREAT, IT WORKED.
NO ONE'S SAD.
YES.
( groaning )
I WIN AGAIN.
HA-HA, THAT'S, LIKE,
500 BUCKS YOU OWE ME.
WHOO-HOO-HOO.
YEAH. $500...
THAT IS A LOT OF ELECTRICITY,
HUH?
WHOO-HOO-HOO.
OOH, I GOT TO BUY SOME FOOD.
OKAY, OKAY, GIVE ME A CHANCE
TO WIN MY MONEY BACK, OKAY?
SUDDEN DEATH, ONE GOAL...
$1,000.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
OH, YES.
OKAY...
GET READY TO OWE ME.
OKAY.
OKAY, HERE WE GO. READY?
NO, NO, NO.
NO.... ONE CAN BEAT ME.
( groaning )
SEE? NOW, THAT'S WHY
ONLY THE LITTLE FAKE MEN
ARE SUPPOSED TO DO THE KICKING.
( phone ringing )
HELLO?
OH, HI, ROSS.
SEE? OTHER PEOPLE CALL ME.
OOH, YOUR BROTHER-- SCORE.
WHAT'S UP?
Oh, I'm just over here with Ben.
THOUGHT WE'D SAY HI.
OH, PUT HIM ON.
BEN, SAY HI TO AUNT MONICA.
OH, I GUESS HE DOESN'T FEEL
LIKE TALKING RIGHT NOW.
UH, HE'S SMILING, THOUGH.
OKAY, TALK TO YOU LATER.
I THINK IT WAS BETTER
WHEN YOU GUYS WERE SAD.
HEY, OH...
REMEMBER THE ROLLERBLADES?
( sobbing ):
OH...
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
I'M NOT GOING TO MISS?
"I'M MONICA. I WASH THE TOILET
17 TIMES A DAY
EVEN IF PEOPLE ARE ON IT."
"HI, I'M RACHEL.
IS MY SWEATER TOO TIGHT?
NO? OH, I BETTER WASH IT
AND SHRINK IT."
"I'M MONICA.
I DON'T GET PHONE MESSAGES
FROM INTERESTING PEOPLE. EVER."
HEY, I CALL HER.
"OH, MY GOD, I LOVE ROSS,
I HATE ROSS.
I LOVE ROSS, I HATE ROSS."
"OH, MY GOD,
I CAN'T FIND A BOYFRIEND
"SO I GUESS I'LL JUST
STUMBLE ACROSS THE HALL
AND SLEEP WITH THE FIRST GUY
I FIND IN THERE."
YEAH, WE SHOULD
GET A MOVE ON
IF WE WANT TO MAKE
THOSE DINNER RESERVATIONS.
STILL BROKEN?
IT SUCKS, MAN.
IT'S YOUR LAST NIGHT HERE
AND I LOSE THE TWO MOST
IMPORTANT THINGS IN MY LIFE--
THE FOOSBALL TABLE AND...
$500.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
THERE ARE OTHER WAYS
YOU CAN WIN BACK YOUR MONEY.
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE,
UH, A LITTLE BLACKJACK?
NAH, NOT MY GAME.
OKAY, UH, HOW ABOUT--
HOW ABOUT...
YOU KNOW, WE COULD
PLAY A NEW GAME.
A NEW GAME-- IT'S FUN.
WELL, WHAT'S IT CALLED?
CUPS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO PLAY CUPS.
I'LL TEACH
YOU. COME ON.
IT'S REAL EASY...
REALLY, REALLY FUN.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, HERE YOU GO.
I HAVE TWO QUEENS.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE?
A TWO AND A FIVE.
HO-HO, YOU WIN, $50.
REALLY?
OH, YEAH. OKAY,
LET'S PLAY AGAIN.
READY?
( chuckling )
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
FOUR AND A NINE.
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
NO. WHY?
WELL, THAT'S A FULL CUP.
DAMN, I AM GOOD AT CUPS.
I'M NOT TALKING TO HER.
ONE OF YOU HAS
TO TAKE THE FIRST STEP
AND IT SHOULD BE YOU
BECAUSE SHE'S THE ONE
WHO'S LEAVING.
IT'S HARDER FOR HER.
WELL, MAYBE
YOU'RE RIGHT...
BUT SHE MADE FUN
OF MY PHONE PEN!
I KNOW.
I TOOK IT HARD, TOO.
LISTEN, RACHEL, I FEEL
REALLY BAD ABOUT WHAT HA...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M UNPACKING.
WHAT?!
I'M NOT MOVING.
IS THAT PICTURE STRAIGHT?
IT NEEDS TO GO
ABOUT 20 BLOCKS TO THE LEFT.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT--
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO WANTS
TO MAKE THIS BIG CHANGE
AND MOVE IN WITH CHANDLER.
YOU SHOULD BE THE ONE TO GO;
WHY DO I HAVE TO LEAVE?
BECAUSE IT'S MY APARTMENT.
WELL, IT'S MINE, TOO.
WHAT ELSE YOU GOT?
HOW ABOUT... YOU'RE MOVING?!
WH...
NO. NO-NO-NO.
YES, YES,
YES-YES-YES.
NO-NO-NO-NO.
YES.
NO-NO-NO.
OKAY, MONICA, WAIT!
COME ON.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
WE SHOULD BE
PACKING YOU!
WH...
Phoebe:
HEY, HOW YOU GUYS DOING?
GREAT.
MONICA'S MOVING.
I AM NOT.
OH, REALLY? WELL, HOW COME
ALL YOUR STUFF IS IN THIS BOX?
OKAY, YOU GUYS, YOU GUYS
I THINK I KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON, HERE, OKAY?
YOU GUYS... STOP!
I KNOW THAT... I KNOW
THAT YOU'RE ACTING MAD
BECAUSE YOU THINK
THAT'LL MAKE IT EASIER TO LEAVE
BUT DEEP DOWN,
YOU'RE STILL REALLY SAD--
DEEP, DEEP DOWN.
NO, PHOEBE, I AM MAD.
WELL, DEEP,
DEEP, DEEP DOWN.
YEAH, I'M JUST MAD.
THEN, KEEP RUNNING.
YOU WIN.
WELL, WHAT DID YOU HAVE?
WELL, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
NOTHING BEATS A...
THREE AND A SIX.
THAT, MY FRIEND,
IS "D" CUP.
OKAY, NOW, HOW MUCH
HAVE YOU WON SO FAR?
UH... WOW...
$700.
NOT $700 EXACTLY?
YEAH.
DOUBLE IT.
WHAT?
YEAH, SEE, IN CUPS
ONCE YOU GET $700,
YOU HAVE TO DOUBLE IT.
REALLY?
HEY, I DIDN'T
MAKE UP THE RULES.
OKAY, SO, NOW
AFTER YOU RECEIVE
THE DOUBLING BONUS
YOU GET, UH, ONE CARD.
NOW, THAT ONE CARD
COULD BE WORTH $100
WHICH BRINGS YOUR
TOTAL TO $1,500.
OH-HO...
NO, WAIT.
DON'T GET TOO EXCITED
BECAUSE THAT'S NOT
GOING TO HAPPEN
UNLESS YOU GET
THE... NO WAY!
WELL, THIS IS THE LAST
BOX OF YOUR CLOTHES.
I'M JUST GOING
TO LABEL IT
"WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?"
HUH, THAT'S SO FUNNY
'CAUSE I WAS JUST GOING TO GO
ACROSS THE HALL
AND WRITE THAT ON CHANDLER.
OKAY, YOU GUYS, I DON'T MEAN
TO MAKE THINGS WORSE
BUT, UM, I DON'T WANT TO LIVE
WITH RACHEL ANYMORE.
WHAT?
YOU'RE JUST SO
MEAN TO EACH OTHER
AND I DON'T WANT
TO END UP LIKE THAT WITH RACHEL.
I STILL LIKE YOU.
WELL, PHOEBE, THAT'S FINE
BECAUSE I'M NOT MOVING.
WHOA-WHOA-WHOA-WHOA-WHOA.
PHOEBE, YOU GOT TO TAKE HER.
I KNOW I SAID
SOME BAD STUFF ABOUT HER
BUT RACHEL DOES HAVE
SOME GOOD QUALITIES
THAT MAKE HER
A GOOD ROOMMATE.
OH, REALLY?
LIKE WHAT, MONICA?
OKAY...
YOU KNOW HOW SHE HAS
147,000 PAIR OF BOOTS?
OH, YEAH, GOOD START, MON.
SHE LETS YOU BORROW THEM.
YEAH, AND YOU STRETCH THEM OUT
WITH YOUR BIG OLD CLOWN FEET.
DO YOU WANT TO LIVE OUTSIDE?
BECAUSE IT'S GETTING COLD.
SHE GETS TONS OF CATALOGS
AND, UM,
SHE'LL FOLD DOWN THE PAGES
OF THE THINGS
THAT SHE THINKS THAT I'D LIKE.
WHAT ELSE?
WELL...
WHEN I TAKE A SHOWER...
SHE LEAVES ME LITTLE NOTES
ON THE MIRROR.
YEAH, I DO.
I-I DO DO THAT.
THAT'S NICE.
I LIKE HAVING THINGS TO READ
IN THE BATHROOM.
WHEN I FALL ASLEEP
ON THE COUCH
AFTER READING...
SHE COVERS ME OVER
WITH A BLANKET.
WELL, YOU KNOW...
I DON'T WANT YOU TO BE COLD.
( voice breaking ):
AND... WHEN I TOLD HER
THAT I WAS GOING TO BE MOVING IN
WITH CHANDLER...
SHE WAS REALLY SUPPORTIVE.
( crying ):
YOU WERE SO GREAT.
YOU MADE IT
SO EASY...
AND, NOW YOU
HAVE TO LEAVE...
AND I HAVE TO
LIVE WITH A BOY!
OH...
OH, HONEY...
( crying )
OH, IT'S GOING TO BE FINE.
OKAY, RACHEL, NOW I CAN'T
WAIT TO LIVE WITH YOU...
AND YOU KNOW WHAT
WE SHOULD DO?
BRING MONICA, AND, THEN
WE COULD ALL LIVE THERE TOGETHER
AND WE'LL HAVE SO MUCH FUN!
BUT, HONEY, I THINK SHE'S
MOVING IN WITH CHANDLER.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE STILL SET ON THAT?
( sniffles )
KIND OF.
OH, MY GOD!
( phone rings )
HELLO?
HEY, MON.
HOW'S THE PACKING GOING?
BEN? HE'S FINE.
YEAH, HE'S RIGHT...
OH, MY GOD!
WELL...
GET YOUR HEAD OUT OF
YOUR SHIRT THERE, SON.
( chuckles nervously )
WHAT?
YEAH, IT'S A PUMPKIN.
I'LL COME PACK.
HEY.
WHAT'S WRONG?
ROSS AND I
WERE HELPING THE GIRLS PACK
TOOK A LITTLE BREAK...
I LOST $1,500 TO HIM AT CUPS.
WHA...
HOW DID YOU LOSE AT CUPS?
THE SAME WAY YOU LOST.
I STARTED OUT WITH
A KING AND A QUEEN.
BAM! ROSS GETS A
TWO AND A THREE.
THEN I GET A JACK AND A KING.
BOOM! ROSS GETS A FOUR AND FIVE.
ROSS WAS GETTING
THE CUP CARD
TH-THE "D" CUP,
THE-THE SITTING-DOWN BONUS...
MEANWHILE, I DIDN'T EVEN GET
A HALF A CUP, NOTHING!
OH, MAN!
HE NEVER PLAYED BEFORE EITHER.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
I THINK BEGINNER'S LUCK--
VERY IMPORTANT IN CUPS.
OKAY, I...
LET'S JUST PLAY ONE MORE HAND--
JUST ONE MORE HAND.
NO, NO, NO MORE--
I CANNOT LOSE ANOTHER DIME.
I'M SERIOUS THIS TIME.
I-IN FACT, LOOK, THERE'S, UH...
I WANT TO GIVE
YOU SOMETHING, OKAY?
AND LET ME GIVE IT TO YOU NOW,
BEFORE I PAWN IT FOR CUPS MONEY.
NOW... I WANT YOU TO HAVE
THE BIG WHITE DOG
AS A... KIND OF A, YOU KNOW
LIKE A THANK YOU FOR...
BEING SUCH A GREAT ROOMMATE.
I CAN'T TAKE THE
BIG WHITE DOG.
YOU LOVE IT.
IT'S "HIM," NOT "IT."
NO, BUT WHAT-WHAT
IF I BOUGHT IT
FROM YOU, YOU KNOW?
AND, THEN, YOUR-YOUR
NICE GESTURE WOULD BE
GIVING IT TO ME
AT A REASONABLE PRICE--
( voice cracking ):
SAY, $1,500?
WAIT A SECOND.
I SEE WHAT YOU'RE TRYING
TO DO HERE.
YOU'RE-YOU'RE-YOU'RE TRYING
TO GIVE ME MONEY AGAIN.
WHEN DID I TRY
TO GIVE YOU MONEY?
BEFORE, OVER THERE,
WITH THE BILLS.
YOU TRIED TO GIVE ME CHARITY.
I SAID, "NO."
YOU DROPPED IT.
OKAY, THEN, WE HAD
A NICE LAST NIGHT TOGETHER.
WE HAD SOME FUN; WE GAMBLED.
NOBODY TRIED
TO GIVE ANYBODY ANY MONEY.
NOW, OUT OF THE BLUE, YOU START
WITH THE CHARITY THING AGAIN.
I'M JUST TRYING
TO HELP YOU OUT, OKAY?
I WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT YOU'RE OKAY.
I WILL BE OKAY.
LOOK, CHANDLER, YOU GOT
TO GET IT OUT OF YOUR HEAD
THAT I CAN'T TAKE CARE
OF MYSELF, OKAY?
LOOK, I'M NOT GOING
TO MISS YOU HELPING ME OUT
WITH MONEY.
THE ONLY THING
THAT I'M GOING TO MISS...
IS YOU...
AND, NOW THE DOG.
HEY...
CALL ME WHEN YOU
GET THERE, OKAY?
OKAY.
I'M REALLY GOING
TO MISS YOU.
MMM.
( both sigh )
OH, I HAVE YOUR KEY.
HERE YOU GO.
THANKS.
OKAY.
OH, GOD, THIS IS SILLY.
I'M GOING TO SEE YOU
IN A COUPLE OF HOURS.
MM-HMM.
BYE, HOUSE.
( chuckling )
BYE, BABE.
BYE.
HI.
SHE REALLY LEFT.
I KNOW.
THANK YOU.
NO PROBLEM, ROOMIE.
CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
SURE.
WHAT THE HELL IS
THAT DOG DOING HERE?
I INVENTED CUPS
AS A WAY TO
GIVE JOEY MONEY.
AND, NOW YOU WANT
THAT MONEY BACK.
EXACTLY.
CHANDLER, WHAT KIND OF IDIOT
DO YOU TAKE ME FOR?
IT'S NOT A REAL GAME.
I MADE IT UP.
I'M SORRY YOU LOST YOUR MONEY,
BUT I WON IT FAIR AND SQUARE.
AT A FAKE GAME!
NOW, IF YOU WANT TO TRY
TO MAKE SOME OF IT BACK...
I'D BE GLAD TO PLAY YOU FOR IT,
BUT I SHOULD WARN YOU--
I AM VERY GOOD AT CUPS.
OKAY...
NOW, I ASSUME
THE SAUCER CARD CAME UP
WHEN YOU PLAYED LAST.
NO.
HMM...
LET'S SEE IF IT COMES UP
THIS TIME.